Voices of Civil Rights Project collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
Guides to the Collections in the Archive of Folk Culture
Voices of Civil Rights Project collection 2003-2004 2003-2006
AFC 2005/015
AARP (Organization)
Library of Congress
History Channel (Television network)
Leadership Conference on Civil Rights
21,395 items; 35 containers; 14 linear feet.
11,200 manuscript items.
101 sound cassettes: analog.
28 microcassettes: analog.
266 sound discs (minidisc) digital; 2 1/2 inch.
4 sound discs (CD-R): digital; 4 3/4 inch.
90 videocassettes (DVCAM): digital, sound, color, 6.35 mm.
193 videocassettes (miniDV): digital, sound, color, 6.35 mm.
19 videocassettes (VHS): sound, color, 1/2 inch.
2 video discs (DVD): digital, sound, color, 4 3/4 inch.
approximately 8000 film negatives: color.
approximately 1492 digital photographs: color, black and white, .jpg, .gif and .tiff files.
Archive of Folk Culture, American Folklife Center, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
Collection consists of oral history interviews, sound and video recordings, photographs and manuscript materials documenting memories of the 20th century civil rights movements in the United States, collected by the American Association of Retired Persons (AARP) from 2003 to 2004 in 48 cities in the South, Midwest and western United States.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
Adams, Victoria Gray, 1926-2006; Andrade, Juan, 1947-; Baxley, Bill (William Joseph), 1941-; Beal, Gerald K., 1933-2011; Beerman, Leonard I., 1921-2014; Boggs, Grace Lee; Bonilla, Rubén, 1946-; Booth, Heather; Bourne, St. Clair, 1943-2007; Bowley, Andy; Branch, Raylawni G., 1941-; Braxton, Annye H., 1933-; Briggs, Jimmie; Brownmiller, Susan; Carlos, John, 1945-; Charles, Michael Ray, 1967-; Collins, Wendell, 1918-; Dahmer, Ellie J., 1925-; Dahmer, Vernon Ferdinand, 1908-1966.; Davis, L. Clifford, 1924-; Dickinson, James Luther; Dinkins, David N.; Doty, Juanita Sims, 1952-; Epps, Jesse, 1936-; Evers, Medgar Wiley, 1925-1963.; Fife, John M. (John Macmillan), 1940-; Fleming, Karl; Forman, James, 1967-; Fountain, Clarence; Frank, Barney, 1940-; Garcia, Isabel (Isabel G.); Gields, Clarence, 1917-2012; Goodman, Carolyn, 1915-2007; Graves, Curtis, 1938-; Green, Percy; Gutiérrez, José Angel; Hackney, Lucy D.; Halpern, Rosario Salgado, 1956-; Hargrove, Earnestine; Harjo, Suzan Shown; Harrington, Penny, 1946-; Hayes, Shirley G., 1936-; Height, Dorothy I. (Dorothy Irene), 1912-2010; Hill, Oliver W., 1907-2007; Hite, Nancy; Holland, Endesha Ida Mae, 1944-2006; Hooks, Benjamin L. (Benjamin Lawson), 1925-2010; Horowitz, Rachelle, 1939-; Iverem, Esther, 1960-; Jarrett, Vernon, 1921-2004; Jones, Doug (G. Douglas), 1954-; Kellogg, Alex; King, B. B.; King, Martin Luther, Jr., 1929-1968.; Kirk, Ron, 1954-; Kochiyama, Yuri; Krol, Debra Utacia; Kwoh, Stewart; Kyles, Samuel Billy; Landrieu, Moon, 1930-2022; Latimer, Leah Y.; Lawson, James M., 1928-; Lee, Helen Shores, 1941-; Lee, Sammy, 1920-2016; Lewis, Dan; Lewis, John, 1940-2020; Little Joe (Vocalist); Lout, Mike (James M.), 1955-; Lowery, Joseph E.; Lum, Lydia; Lyons, Kenneth O., 1941-; Mapp, Marilyn; Marquez Stathis, Sandra; Mashariki, Job, 1943-; McKinstry, Carolyn Maull, 1948-; McWhorter, Diane; Mease, Quentin R., 1908-2009; Meier, Deborah; Miller, Tom, 1947-; Mingo, Lucy, 1931-; Monroe, Sputnik, 1928-2006; Moses, Robert Parris; Moutoussamy-Ashe, Jeanne, 1951-; Murray, Tawanda, 1974-; Neubauer, Rita; Norton, Eleanor Holmes; O'Konis, Jonathan; Oldham, Charles R.; Patoski, Joe Nick, 1951-; Pierce, Ponchitta Anne, 1942-; Poussaint, Alvin F.; Pride, Carlton, 1966-; Reavis, Dick J.; Reid, Vernon; Rivers, Eugene; Romilly, Constancia; Rosenfeld, Megan; Rosenzweig, Hannah; Rowles, Billy E., 1945-; Seay, Norman R., 1932-; Sellers, Cleveland, 1944-; Shores, Barbara, 1945-; Sims, Bernice Banks; Sloan, Lester; Smith, Jerome M., 1939-; Smith, Vern E.; Spellman-Diaz, Toyin, 1973-; Steger, Michelle, 1967-; Sutton, Goodloe, 1939-; Swann-Daniels, Carol, 1948-; Tafel, Richard; Thompson, Larry Dean, 1945-; Tisdale, Alice, 1955-; Tisdale, Charles, 1926-; Trickey, Minnijean Brown; Uyeshima, Erin Emiko; West, W. Richard; Whitehouse, Liz; Wilder, Lawrence Douglas, 1931-; Wilkins, Roger W., 1932-2017; Williams, Juan.; Wilson, Diane, 1948-; Wilson, Edwin O., 1943-; Wolf, Bonny; Wunrow, Jeffrey D., 1967-; Yamamoto, Joyce C.; Ynclan, Nery; Zabel, William D.
Organizations
AARP (Organization); History Channel (Television network); Leadership Conference on Civil Rights; Library of Congress; March on Washington for Jobs and Freedom (1963: Washington, D.C.); Selma to Montgomery Rights March (1965: Selma, Ala.); Topeka (Kan.). Board of Education--Trials, litigation, etc.
Subjects
African Americans--Civil rights--Interviews.; Civil rights demonstrations--United States--History--20th century.; Civil rights movements--United States--History--20th century.; Discrimination in education--United States--History--20th century.; Discrimination in employment--United States--History--20th century.; Discrimination in the military--United States--History--20th century.; Gay rights--United States--History--20th century.; Hispanic Americans--Civil rights--Interviews.; Indians of North America--Civil rights--Interviews.; People with disabilities--Civil rights--Interviews.; School integration--Arkansas--Little Rock.; School integration--United States--History--20th century.; School integration--Virginia--Prince Edward County.; Segregation in education--United States--History--20th century.; Segregation in transportation--Southern States--History--20th century.
Places
United States--Race relations--History--20th century.
Form/Genre
Digital photographs--Color--2000-2010.; Film negatives--Color--2000-2010.; Interviews.; Oral histories.; Sound recordings.; Transcripts.; Videocassettes.
Acquisition
The Voices of Civil Rights Project collection was accessioned at the Library of Congress in 2005 and 2006. The Veterans History Project originally held custody of the collection until it was transferred to the Archive of Folk Culture in September 2005.
Accruals
No further accruals are expected.
Bibliography
The Library of Congress. Exhibitions: Voices of Civil Rights. May 26, 2005. http://www.loc.gov/exhibits/civilrights/
The Library of Congress. “Voices of Civil Rights: U.S. Civil Rights Movement is Subject of Exhibition.” The Library Today. Information Bulletin: An online companion to the Library’s monthly magazine. March 2005. http://www.loc.gov/loc/lcib/0503/rights.html
A&E Television Networks. History Channel. Save Our History: Voices of Civil Rights. 1999-2006.
Williams, Juan. My Soul Looks Back In Wonder: Voices of the Civil Rights Experience. AARP, Sterling, 2004.
"AARP and LCCR Announce the Official Launch of VoicesofCivilRights.org," March 30, 2004. http://www.aarp.org/about-aarp/press-center/info-2004/civilrights_1.1.html
Access and Restrictions
Collection is open for research. Access to recordings may be restricted. Duplication of the collection materials may be governed by copyright and other restrictions. To request materials, please contact the Folklife Reading Room at http://hdl.loc.gov/loc.afc/folklife.contact
Organizational History
Inspired by the 50th anniversary of the Brown v. Board of Education Supreme Court decision, the American Association of Retired Persons (AARP), the Leadership Conference on Civil Rights (LCCR), and the Library of Congress initiated the Voices of Civil Rights (VOCR) Project in 2003 to collect and preserve stories of individuals who took part in, witnessed, or were affected by the civil rights movement. The Voices of Civil Rights Project was launched in August of 2004 with an event on the National Mall hosted by WJLA's Maureen Bunyan. The History Channel also participated in filming interviews, some of which were used for documentaries produced by the television station. Selected materials were on view at the Library through March 26, 2005; afterwards, the original project materials were accessioned in the Library's collection and curated by the American Folklife Center.
Scope and Content Note
The manuscript submissions consist of correspondence from AARP members who responded to invitations in AARP Magazine and AARP Bulletin asking members to send in written vignettes of 500 words or less describing their civil rights experiences. This call for submissions was broadened when AARP published another invitation to general readers of the Sunday newspaper magazine Parade. Once the project had gained momentum, individuals were also able to submit their written experiences through the Voices of Civil Rights website and email. In addition, some interviewees from the bus tour also submitted written accounts. The majority of the 1,612 submissions are 1-2 pages; some participants included longer reminiscences and other items such as photographs and copies of related news articles.
The book My Soul Looks Back in Wonder is a collection of essays based on original audio interviews with 33 individuals. Authored by journalist Juan Williams, this book focuses on the experiences of both leaders and ordinary people who participated in or were affected by civil rights movements. This collection includes audio interviews with 82 people considered for the book, transcripts, book chapter drafts, and background research conducted for the book and submitted to AARP at the close of the project.
Beginning in Washington, D.C. on August 3, 2004, the bus tour traveled part of the 1961 Freedom Riders route and covered 48 cities in three months. By the conclusion of the tour, nearly 200,000 people had attended Voices of Civil Rights events in their communities. VOCR kick-off events with speeches and musical performances by local groups were held at many of the major cities that were visited, and audio and video documentation of these events are included in this collection. Still image documentation of the entire project was captured on digital and negative film. The team of journalists assembled for this project conducted the majority of the bus audio/video oral histories, capturing them on minidiscs and Digital Video (DV) tapes. In addition to interviews captured by the project staff, a team from the History Channel also conducted video interviews for joint use by the History Channel and the project. There are approximately 1158 audio interviews with 32 corresponding transcripts and approximately 569 video interviews with 47 corresponding transcripts in this collection.
The administrative materials generated by AARP to track the growing collection of materials is also included in this collection and consists of promotional and press materials, Excel spreadsheets, inventory lists, and interviewer log notes.
Arrangement
The collection is divided into five series. Series I: Manuscripts includes email, mail, and web form submissions of individuals' experiences, thoughts, reminiscences of the civil rights movement, and administrative materials (Series II, III and IV also include transcripts). Series II: My Soul Looks Back in Wonder Interviews includes original audio interviews, transcripts, book drafts and relevant background research on individuals involved in the civil rights movement for the book My Soul Looks Back In Wonder, edited by Juan Williams. Series III: Bus Tour Interviews and Events Sound Recordings includes original audio interviews and transcripts recorded by Voices of Civil Rights staff and contract reporters on the bus tour across the U.S. and at other related events. Series IV: Bus Tour Interviews and Events Moving Images includes original video interviews and transcripts recorded by Voices of Civil Rights staff, contract reporters and History Channel staff on the bus tour across the U.S. Series V: Bus Tour Interviews and Events Graphic Images includes digital and film still images of Voices of Civil Rights participants, interviewees and locations taken during the bus tour across the U.S.
Container List
- Series I: Manuscripts, 2003-2006
  Subseries I contains administrative materials generated by AARP staff to track the collection of materials including promotional and press materials, emails, Excel spreadsheets, inventory lists, and interviewer log notes. Subseries II contains the manuscript submissions from AARP members who responded to invitations in AARP Magazine and AARP Bulletin asking members to send in written vignettes of 500 words or less describing their civil rights experiences. This call for submissions was broadened when AARP published another invitation to general readers of the Sunday newspaper magazine Parade. The general public was also able to submit their written experiences through the Voices of Civil Rights website and email. In addition, some interviewees from the bus tour also submitted written accounts. The majority of the 1,612 submissions are 1-2 pages; some participants included longer reminiscences and other items such as photographs and copies of related news articles.
  - Subseries I: Administrative, 2003-2006, 29 folders
    - Finding aid (Box-folder 1/1)
    - Background research (Box-folder 1/2)
    - Bus tour planning (Box-folder 1/3)
    - Press materials (Box-folder 1/4)
    - Bus tour press clips printouts (4 folders) (Box-folder 1/5-8)
      599 original PDF files also available.
    - Promotional items (Box-folder 1/9)
    - Checklist sent by Arkansas state office (Box-folder 2/1)
    - Series I spreadsheets (Box-folder 2/2)
    - Series II background (Box-folder 2/3)
    - Series III spreadsheets (Box-folder 2/4)
    - Series III copies of tape envelopes (2 folders) (Box-folder 2/5-6)
    - Series IV spreadsheets (Box-folder 2/7)
    - Interviewer biographies (Box-folder 2/8)
    - Interviewer log notes: Iverem, Esther (Box-folder 2/9)
    - Interviewer log notes: Krol, Debra (Box-folder 2/10)
    - Interviewer log notes: Lum, Lydia (Box-folder 2/11)
    - Interviewer log notes: Mapp, Marilyn (Box-folder 2/12)
    - Interviewer log notes: Marquez, Sandra (Box-folder 2/13)
    - Interviewer log notes: Neubauer, Rita (Box-folder 2/14)
    - Interviewer log notes: O'Konis, Jonathan (Box-folder 2/15)
    - Interviewer log notes: Patoski, Joe Nick (Box-folder 2/16)
    - Interviewer log notes: Smith, Vern (Box-folder 2/17)
    - Interviewer log notes: Whitehouse, Liz (Box-folder 2/18)
    - Interviewer log notes: Ynclan, Nery (Box-folder 2/19)
    - Interviewer top ten (Box-folder 2/20)
  - Subseries II: Submissions, 2003-2004, 1612 folders
    - Abernathy, James (Box-folder 3/1)
      Includes essay and news clippings.
    - Abram, Betzi (Box-folder 3/2)
    - Adams, Annie Lorraine Harris (Box-folder 3/3)
    - Adams, Bonnie Jean (Box-folder 3/4)
    - Adams, Cindi L. (Box-folder 3/5)
    - Adams, Frank R. (Box-folder 3/6)
    - Adelekan, Patricia (Box-folder 3/7)
    - Adkins, Jeanne Johns (Box-folder 3/8)
    - Adler, Joe (Box-folder 3/9)
    - Agerton, Barbara (Box-folder 3/10)
    - Agovino, William (Box-folder 3/11)
    - Akers, Edwin (Box-folder 3/12)
    - Albers, Kathy (Box-folder 3/13)
    - Aldridge, Gwendolyn (Box-folder 3/14)
    - Alessi, Janice C. Lawyer (Box-folder 3/15)
    - Alford, John M. (Box-folder 3/16)
      Contains several letters.
    - Alguire, Esther M. (Box-folder 3/17)
    - Allen, Ernest, Sr. (Box-folder 3/18)
      Includes brief web biographies of Roy Innis and James Farmer.
    - Allen, Robert (Box-folder 3/19)
      Includes photographs and clippings.
    - Allen, Victoria Velarde (Box-folder 3/20)
    - Allison, Marva (Box-folder 3/21)
    - Alm, Glenda Kaser (Box-folder 3/22)
    - Alpert, Lisa (Box-folder 3/23)
    - Alstrom, Gayle (Box-folder 3/24)
    - Alvero, M. Carmelita (Box-folder 3/25)
    - Amaro, Gilbert (Box-folder 3/26)
    - Amussen, Diane (Box-folder 3/27)
    - Ancrum, Rosa (Box-folder 3/28)
    - Anderson, Betty (Box-folder 3/29)
    - Anderson, Dorothy Jones (Box-folder 3/30)
      Contains photograph.
    - Anderson, D. M. (Box-folder 3/31)
    - Anderson, Hans (Box-folder 3/32)
    - Anderson, Oretha (Box-folder 3/33)
    - Anderson, Paul I. (Box-folder 3/34)
    - Anderson-Jones, Carole Moody (Box-folder 3/35)
    - Andrews, Charles R. (Box-folder 3/36)
    - Andrews, Janet (Box-folder 3/37)
    - Andrews, Lester E., Sr. (Box-folder 3/38)
    - Andrews, Linda (Box-folder 3/39)
    - Andrews, Suzanne (Box-folder 3/40)
    - Anonymous (Box-folder 3/41)
    - Anthony, Antonie (Box-folder 3/42)
    - Anthony, Gloria J. (Box-folder 3/43)
    - Applegate, Lloyd Rogers (Box-folder 3/44)
    - Arens, Dorothy (Box-folder 3/45)
    - Arledge, H. Linda Lucas Keith (Box-folder 3/46)
    - Armstrong, Anna M. (Box-folder 3/47)
    - Armstrong, Elaine P. (Box-folder 3/48)
    - Armstrong, Norma Jean (Box-folder 3/49)
    - Arnold, John M. (Box-folder 3/50)
    - Arnold, Robert S. (Box-folder 3/51)
    - Ary, Jesse (Box-folder 3/52)
    - Ash, Brenda Barnhill (Box-folder 3/53)
    - Ashton, Ellen (Box-folder 3/54)
    - Askew, Esther (Box-folder 3/55)
    - Atkinson, Charles Henry (Box-folder 3/56)
    - Audritsh, Jim (Box-folder 3/57)
    - Auerbach, Danny (Box-folder 3/58)
    - Aukema, Richard L. (Box-folder 3/59)
      Includes essay.
    - Austin, April (Box-folder 3/60)
    - Austin, Robert B., Jr. (Box-folder 3/61)
    - Avalos, Gloria J. (Box-folder 3/62)
    - Ayers, Deborah (Box-folder 3/63)
    - Ayres, Douglas W. (Box-folder 3/64)
    - Azibo, Ekundayo (Box-folder 3/65)
    - Babayan, Levon (Box-folder 4/1)
    - Babian, Michelle (Box-folder 4/2)
    - Badgley, Lois K. (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Bagby, Grover C. (Box-folder 4/4)
    - Bailey, Joseph A., II (Box-folder 4/5)
      Includes news clippings.
    - Baker, Ilse Heinigen (Box-folder 4/6)
    - Baker, James W. (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Ball, Edwin and Janice (Box-folder 4/8)
    - Ball, John T. (Box-folder 4/9)
    - Ball, Josephine (Box-folder 4/10)
    - Ballentine, Krim M. (Box-folder 4/11)
      Includes photograph and letter.
    - Balsley, Ken (Box-folder 4/12)
    - Banks, Frank K. (Box-folder 4/13)
    - Banks-Bey, Donna (Box-folder 4/14)
    - Barclift, Sunny (Box-folder 4/15)
    - Barnes, Dorothy M. (Box-folder 4/16)
    - Barr, Katharine (Box-folder 4/17)
    - Barron, Jim (Box-folder 4/18)
    - Bartoletti, Mario D. (Box-folder 4/19)
    - Baskerville, Lezli (Box-folder 4/20)
    - Bauer, Keith L. (Box-folder 4/21)
    - Baughman, Dorothy (Box-folder 4/22)
    - Baum, John A. (Box-folder 4/23)
    - Baumann, Hilde (Box-folder 4/24)
    - Bayley, Erma J. (Box-folder 4/25)
    - Beacham, Toni (Box-folder 4/26)
    - Beal, Gerald Kenneth (Box-folder 4/27)
    - Beck, Dessie (Box-folder 4/28)
    - Beck, Orene (Box-folder 4/29)
    - Beckley, Erma L. McFadden (Box-folder 4/30)
    - Beland, Edwin F. (Box-folder 4/31)
    - Bell, Donald R. (Box-folder 4/32)
    - Bell, Minerva Mills (Box-folder 4/33)
    - Bell, Norva S. (Box-folder 4/34)
    - Bell, Virginia M. (Box-folder 4/35)
    - Benard, Patricia (Box-folder 4/36)
    - Bend, Wilbert, Sr. (Box-folder 4/37)
    - Bendan, Ann (Box-folder 4/38)
    - Benedetti, Frank (Box-folder 4/39)
    - Benigno, Russell A. (Box-folder 4/40)
    - Bennett, Wilma E. (Box-folder 4/41)
    - Bennett-Purnell, Rosentene (Box-folder 4/42)
    - Benson, Michael (Box-folder 4/43)
    - Bergins, Annette (Box-folder 4/44)
    - Berkebile, Jessie V. (Box-folder 4/45)
    - Berry, Janet (Box-folder 4/46)
    - Berry, Judith C. (Box-folder 4/47)
    - Berryman, Betty Ward (Box-folder 4/48)
    - Bethany Academy students (Box-folder 4/49)
    - Betts, Karen R. (Box-folder 4/50)
    - Beyer, Daniel P. (Box-folder 4/51)
    - Bice, Roma (Box-folder 4/52)
    - Biddle, Jerry Sue (Box-folder 4/53)
    - Billingslea, Elizabeth Walker (Box-folder 4/54)
    - Bird, James R. (Box-folder 4/55)
    - Birtha, Herbert M. (Box-folder 4/56)
    - Bivens, La Juana (Box-folder 4/57)
    - Black, Ruthie Harris (Box-folder 4/58)
    - Blackmon, Thelma (Box-folder 4/59)
    - Bladholm, H. Ann (Box-folder 4/60)
    - Blanchard, Sandra M. (Box-folder 4/61)
    - Bland, James (Box-folder 4/62)
      Includes flyers and poems.
    - Blanton, Thomas (Box-folder 4/63)
    - Bleidorn, Eugene F. (Box-folder 4/64)
      Includes book.
    - Blivin, Evelyn (Box-folder 4/65)
    - Blocker, Dave (Box-folder 4/66)
    - Blocker, Karen A. (Box-folder 4/67)
    - Bloom, Diane (Box-folder 4/68)
      Includes media packet.
    - Bluestone, Fred (Box-folder 4/69)
    - Blumenthal, Iris S. (Box-folder 4/70)
    - Bogart, Betty (Box-folder 5/1)
    - Bond, Noah W. (Box-folder 5/2)
    - Booker, Robert J. (Box-folder 5/3)
    - Booth, Grace (Box-folder 5/4)
    - Bordelon, Dena C. Y. (Box-folder 5/5)
    - Borden, G. A. (Box-folder 5/6)
    - Borgman, Robert D. (Box-folder 5/7)
    - Bosco, Antoinette (Box-folder 5/8)
    - Bowden, William Stephen (Box-folder 5/9)
    - Bowman, Sherrie P. (Box-folder 5/10)
    - Boyer, Dennis (Box-folder 5/11)
    - Bracy, LaVon W. (Box-folder 5/12)
    - Bradford, Arlonial Delaine (Box-folder 5/13)
    - Brady, Patti (Box-folder 5/14)
    - Braman, Gail W. (Box-folder 5/15)
    - Brandon, Brumsic, Jr. (Box-folder 5/16)
    - Braunschweiger, Dorine (Box-folder 5/17)
    - Braxton, Frank (Box-folder 5/18)
    - Braxton, Herman (Box-folder 5/19)
    - Bready, Mary H. (Box-folder 5/20)
    - Breedlove, Gloria Jean Westbrooks (Box-folder 5/21)
      Includes theater program.
    - Bressack, Alfred (Box-folder 5/22)
    - Brett, Robert (Box-folder 5/23)
    - Bridgers, Earline (Box-folder 5/24)
    - Brinkley, Samuel Bernard (Box-folder 5/25)
    - Brisbane, Kathleen (Box-folder 5/26)
    - Brisben, J. Quinn (Box-folder 5/27)
    - Briscoe-Wilson, Elizabeth Ann (Box-folder 5/28)
    - Britts, Maurice W. (Box-folder 5/29)
    - Brodie, William R. (Box-folder 5/30)
    - Broms, Ellen (Box-folder 5/31)
      Includes photographs and an administrative email.
    - Brooks, James (Box-folder 5/32)
    - Brooks, Shera (Box-folder 5/33)
    - Brookter, Sylvia Atlow (Box-folder 5/34)
    - Brown, C. Sybil (Box-folder 5/35)
    - Brown, Dale (Box-folder 5/36)
    - Brown, Frances Johnson (Box-folder 5/37)
    - Brown, Geoffrey (Box-folder 5/38)
    - Brown, Ilene B. (Box-folder 5/39)
    - Brown, James E. (Box-folder 5/40)
    - Brown, Janice (Box-folder 5/41)
    - Brown, Janice Lattimore (Box-folder 5/42)
    - Brown, Lannie Jean (Box-folder 5/43)
    - Brown, Laura Jeanette (Box-folder 5/44)
    - Brown, Linda Beatrice (Box-folder 5/45)
    - Brown, M. Betty (Box-folder 5/46)
    - Brown, O. C. (Box-folder 5/47)
      Includes news clippings and maps.
    - Brown, Paul (Box-folder 5/48)
    - Brown, Raymond R. (Box-folder 5/49)
    - Brown, Thomas D. (Box-folder 5/50)
    - Brown, Warren L. (Box-folder 5/51)
    - Brown-Graham, Barbara (Box-folder 5/52)
    - Brown-Williams, Jacqueline (Box-folder 5/53)
    - Broyles, Catalina (Box-folder 5/54)
    - Bruno, Martha Woods (Box-folder 5/55)
    - Bryan, Polly K. (Box-folder 5/56)
    - Bryant, Carolyn (Box-folder 5/57)
    - Bryson, Lucille (Box-folder 5/58)
    - Buchanan, Elnora Thomas (Box-folder 5/59)
    - Buck, Angeline P. (Box-folder 5/60)
    - Buckles, Theresa (Box-folder 5/61)
    - Buckley, Linda (Box-folder 5/62)
    - Buie, Orma W. (Box-folder 5/63)
    - Bunce, Betty S. (Box-folder 5/64)
    - Burke, Ed R. (Box-folder 5/65)
    - Burke, Virginia C. (Box-folder 5/66)
    - Burke, William (Box-folder 5/67)
    - Burnett, John (Box-folder 5/68)
    - Burns, Elaine (Box-folder 5/69)
    - Burns, Elva Messick (Box-folder 5/70)
    - Burns, Sid G. (Box-folder 5/71)
    - Burrows, Arlene Blaier (Box-folder 5/72)
    - Burton, Charles Wesley (Box-folder 5/73)
    - Busby, Linda (Box-folder 5/74)
    - Bustamante, Ernest (Box-folder 5/75)